Svyatoslav Polishchuk

www.polishchuk.design svyat@polishchuk.design 07903 809381

Profile

A fast-learning and meticulous product designer who finds answers. Therefore delivers effective solutions and delightful experiences by undertaking complex business and social challenges. And therefore works across multiple disciplines with a focus on cross-platform strategy, interaction and user experience.

Experience

Karabeen.com — Freelance Product Designer

Formulated and translated business needs into digital solutions to meet user needs and enhance products for several clients and startups in over 15 projects.

September 2015 - October 2018

SoPost - UX/UI Design Intern

Worked in Platform team to design and build new internal tools automating routine tasks for commercial team and excluding developers input from the process. Also supported single design language implementation across all internal systems and establishing UI foundation by developing an extended Bootstrap theme.

May 2017 - August 2017

Binary Studio — UX/UI Designer

Worked with executive and marketing team to find suitable digital and branding solutions enabling the company to grow faster and build a better employer brand. Consulted a few software projects to deliver exceptional user experience.

May 2016 - August 2016

Happy Design — UX/UI Designer

Designed websites, information architecture and complex web and mobile user interfaces to meet business and user needs for a wide range of companies and early-stage startups.

Tools

July 2014 - September 2015

Design

Skills

Product thinking Adobe Suite
Interaction design Sketch
User research InVision
User experience design Principle

Usability testing Front-end development (HTML / CSS / JS)

Education

Northumbria University — BA (Hons) Interaction Design

2015 - 2018, 1st class

Lviv Polytechnic — BArch Urban Planning

2000 - 2014, 2:1